A Guide to the Maps and flat files FA465
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller, 2
  - Homes, 2.I
    - Rockefeller & Satterlee boundary lines, present and proposed., 1930 September; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 1)
      Homes, Map #73. "#192, Saterlee property."
    - Ampitheater road bridge over Little Harbor Brook. Mt. Desert Estate of JDR Jr. (Charles Houghton), 1930 November 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 1)
      Homes, Map #74. Progress print, sheet #2
    - Ampitheater road bridge over Little Harbor Brook. Mt. Desert Estate of JDR Jr. (Charles Houghton), 1930 November 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #79. Progress print, sheet #1
    - Alternate designs for causeway across Otter Creek. (Van Beuren, Stanley), 1925 November 19; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #75. Notes on reverse: "#172D, Otter Creek bridge, Mr. Dunns letter of April 1930"; "Homes OMR map 122 b123 f1242"
    - Bridge #1 Asticou-Jordan Pond Road. Mt Desert Estate, JDR Jr. (Charles Houghton), Revised:1930 October 22 and November 6; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #76.
      Reverse: "OMR Homes, Box 122, folder 1226, map 76"
    - Lamp standards and bases for causeway across Otter Creek. (J.G. White Engineering Corporation), 1926 October 14; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Hokmes, Map #77. Reverse: "#172A, Otter Creek Bridge, Mr. Dunn's Letter, April 1930"
    - Ampitheater road bridge over Little Harbor Brook. Mt. Desert Estate of JDR Jr. (Charles Houghton), Approved: 1930 January 7; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #78. Copy of blueprint #196, received with Mr. C, letter of Jan 7"
      Box 123, folder 1241.
    - Plan of Jordan Pond Road underpass, Bridge #4. JDR Jr. Engineering, Seal Harbor, Maine (JDR Jr. Engineering?), 1931 October 17; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #80. with pencil markings. Reverse. "#235 Change SH Water Co Pipes over bridge #4. From Mr. Simpson, 10/26/1931"
    - Plan showing property of David Rockefeller at Seal Harbor. (Maurice H. Burr), 1960 November; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #81
    - Survey of property of JDR Jr. in Tarrytown (Chas. H. Sells), 1957 September 3-6; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #82.
    - Alterations to "Westways", Seal Harbor, Maine (Arthur W. McFarland), undated; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #83. Reverse: #556a, Oct 1947, Basement floor plan for Westway (file- SH, David R.)"
    - Seal Harbor estate office, undated; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #84. Reverse: "Copy #2, #558, S.H. Estate Office, Floor Plans, Oct. 1947 (File SH David R.)"
    - Seal Harbor estate office, undated; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #85. Reverse: "Copy #1, #558, S.H. Estate Office, Floor Plans, Oct. 1947 (File SH David R.)"
    - Alterations to "Westways" - Elevator. JDR Jr. (Arthur W. McFarland), undated; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #86. Reverse: "Map #563, see from Arthur McFarland, Jan. 1948, files SH - David R - sub fd)"
    - Plan showing property of JDR, NAR, & DR at Seal Harbor (Maurice H. Burr), 1958 December; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #87. Pencil markings. Reverse: "1958, NAR/DR prop, SH"
    - Estate Realty Co. Park, 1935 March 1; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #88. "SH David Rockefeller"
    - Plan of land conveyed to DR by JDR Jr (illegible), 1954; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #89.
    - Floor plans, Long Pond Lodge, 1947 August 29; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #90. Reverse: "Mr. Derevere's house." "#557, Oct. 1947" "Floor plans, Long Pond Lodge (File SH - DR - sub fd)"
    - Rear elevation, Alteration to Westways, for JDR Jr (Arthur W. McFarland), undated; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #91. Reverse: "David Dining Room, #556, Oct 1947, Realterations to Westways dining room" "File- SH - David R"
    - Boat house property of Mr. Nelson A Rockefeller, Islesford, Maine (n/a), 1939; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #92. Accompanying note to Ms. Wayford.
    - Part of Bar Harbor, Town of Eden, ME (Summer Residents Association of Bar Harbor), 1903; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #93. Lots of pencil markings. Reverse: "#525 from Mr. Rodrick, Sept 6, 1941"
    - Hand-drawn map of Roscoe B. Jackson Memorial Laboratory, preliminary study (Olmstead Brothers), 1950 March 20. Revised: 1950 May 15; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #94. Reverse: "Map #599 received for file Sept 1950, SH landscaping folder"
    - Map of Jackson Memorial Laboratory, with handwritten notes (Simpson), undated; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #95. Reverse: "Simpson map #594, showing prop. Adjoining Sanford lot, which Mr Hadley suggests being trans. To jackson Memorial Lab. Sent by Mr Simpson 10/24/49"
    - Great Meadow Hill area, Acadia Nat'l Park and adjoining properties. (Simpson), 1948 November 5; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #96. Reverse: "Map #578, Simpson map showing great meadow area." "Copy of ours sent little recently. Simpson, 12/15/48"
    - Land being deeded from JDR JR to Jackson Memorial Laboratory (P.D. Simpson), 1948 December 15; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #97. Reverse: "#579, Simpson map showing meter and bounds of 8 acre tract being deeded to Jackson Memorial Lab" "SH - Jackson Memorial Lab - Gift Folder"
    - Hand-drawn map on tissue paper. Plan showing ownership of land on Dodge's Point, 1937 August 11; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #98. Reverse: "Dodge Point #420, from Mr. Simpson, Aug 11, 1930"
    - Plan showing proposed addition to village park, 1936 April; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #99. Reverse: "#114 copy 2 of print sent with Jr's letter of june 15, 1936, to _____ of Mt Desert"
    - Proposed parking area in Mount Desert (P.D. Simpson), 1950 September 20; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #100. Reverse: "Re enlargement of parking area near beach area, sent by Paul Simpson, Sept 21, 1950"
    - Hand-drawn map on tissue paper. Map of Town of Mount Desert. (Simpson?), 1932 September-October; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #101. Reverse: "#288 from Mr. Simpson, Nov. 2, 1932, SH Beach Ownership" "SH VIL. _______"
    - JDR Jr property, 1931 July 30; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #102. Reverse: "#224A, Blueprint showing piece of property owned by the village green?" "Reff.8-1931"
    - Hand-drawn map on tissue paper. Map of roads around dam with lots of notes, undated; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #103.
    - Map of street changes, Sutton Place, 53rd, 54th, 55th, 60th, East River Drive, York Avenue between 54-59th (Department of Public Works/M. Goldberg), 1937 March 4; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #104. Received Dec 7, 1937
    - Section of map of East River Drive, undated; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #105. Received Dec 7, 1937
    - Map of the Mallory estate, Pocantico Hills (Henry C. Thompson), 1891 October 12; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #106.
    - Map of the Mallory estate, Pocantico Hills (Henry C. Thompson), 1891 October 12; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #107.
    - Map of Property in Pocantico Hills, 1960 July 27; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #108. Colored to show property lines
    - Water Service plan, Recreation Center, Mount Pleasant, New York, 1958 October 15. Revised: 1958 November 7; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 2)
      Homes, Map #109.
    - Proposed motor road, E. Side Tarn, #5 (Walter Kidde Constructors), 1930 August 19; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #110.
    - Plot plan, Bubble Pond Bridge, Lafayette National Park (Department of the Interior and the National Park Service), undated; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #111. Reverse: "Bubble Pond bridge #80 copy 2, from Mr. Cremmerer, Oct 15, 1927. Attached to letter."
    - Proposed motor road, Bridge at Kebo Brook (Walter Kidde Constructors), 1930 August; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #112.
    - Proposed lower horse road at Harden Farm (Walter Kidde Constructors), 1930 August 20; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #113.
    - Road parapets: alternative copings for Stanley Brook, Acadia National Park (Olmstead Brothers/E.L. Whiting?), 1934 August 3; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #118. Reverse: "Stamped - issued by the Olmsted Bros, Brookline Mass, Aug 3, 1934" "#353 Olmstead letter 8/3/34" "SH Stanley B. K. Bridge"
    - Sieur de Monts Spring Bridge (Arthur W. McFarland), undated; RENDERING (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #114. Reverse: "Sent by McFarland Oct 27, 1952" "SH Bridges"
      Box 121, Folder 1216.
    - Stanley Brook Road, Bridge A, Mt Desert Estate of JDR Jr (Charles Houghton), 1934 August 10; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #115.
      Box 121, Folder 1219.
    - Stanley Brook Road, Bridge A, Mt Desert Estate of JDR Jr (Charles Houghton), 1934 August 10; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #116.
    - Stanley Brook Road culverts, Mt Desert Estate of JDR Jr (Charles Houghton), 1934 August 10; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #117. #356
    - Pencil drawings on tissue of Stanley Brook Road Bridge A., undated; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 6) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #119. Reverse: "#354 Sketches Stanley B Bridge, from Mr. Simpson, August 20 1934"
    - Stanley Brook Culvert 2, Mt Desert Estate of JDR Jr (Charles Houghton), 1934 August 24; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #120. Reverse: "#355 Stanley Brook Bridge, Mr Stoughton, August 1934"
    - Study of bridge over dam for causeway across Otter Creek (J.G. White Engineering Corporation), 1926 October 14; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #121. #172 Otter Creek Bridge, Mr Dunn's letter of April 1930
    - Bridge #1 Asticou-Jordan Pond Road. Mt Desert Estate, JDR Jr. (Charles Houghton), undated; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #122. Reverse: "December 1930"
    - Study of bridge over dam for causeway across Otter Creek (J.G. White Engineering Corporation), 1926 November; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #123. Reverse: "#172b Otter Creek Bridge, Mr. Dunn's Letter of April 1930"
    - Sketch of Bridge over 59th Street Lake, Central Park, New York (W.R. Pearsall), undated; RENDERING (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #124. "Similar to stone bridge in Seal Harbor, Maine" Stamped office of JDR Jr "#44" "Mr. R Says this is the bridle path bridge"
    - Elevations for stone bridge, Seal Harbor, Maine (Welles-Bosworth), 1919 March 28. Revised and approved: 1919 May 12; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #125. Reverse: "Hadlock Pond bridge" "#45" "This is the little harbor brook bridge?"
    - Elevation of Deer Brook Trail bridge, undated; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #126. Reverse: "Office of JDR Jr, Bridges" "#48 Deer Brook Bridge - Horse Road built by M. Clement" "Received for file may 26, 1925"
    - Bridge at Deer Brook Crossing on Jordan-Sargeant Mountain Road (Welles-Bosworth), 1925 June 2; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #127. Reverse: "Office of JDR Jr, Deer Brook Bridge, June 8 1925, from Mr. Pearsall, #47, with letter June 12, 1925, from Mr. Simpson"
    - Jordan-Sargeant Mountain Road, site of Chasm Brook Bridge (none), undated; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #128. Reverse: "#46 attached to Pearsall letter of Feb 1, 1936, Chasm Brook Bridge"
    - Pencil sketch of bridge, double sided (none), undated; RENDERING (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #129. Double-sided.
    - Horse bridge, Seal Harbor (Welles-Bosworth), 1926 September 29. Revised: 1926 October 14; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #131. Reverse: "#84 Horse Bridge, second design, Bubble Point"
    - Horse bridge, Seal Harbor (Welles-Bosworth), 1926 September 29; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #132. Reverse: "Horse road designs, square posts, #83"
    - Horse bridge, Seal Harbor, Lafayette National Park, undated; RENDERING (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #133. reverse: "#81 Bubble Pond Horse Bridge"
    - Hemlock Bridge, undated; RENDERING (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #134. Reverse: "#43 from Simpson, Dec 24, 1923"
    - Bridge #1 on the Astico-Jordan Road, Mt. Desert Estate, JDR Jr (Charles Houghton), 1930 October 15; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #135. Reverse: "From A.B. Cammerer, oct. 20 1930"
    - Eagle Lake Brook bridge, Estate of JDR Jr Mount Desert (Charles Houghton), 1929 June 11; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, #136. Reverse: "SH Bridges, Not Built, Cedar Bridge substituted" stamped June 21, 1929
    - Eagle Lake Bridge, Mt. Desert, (Charles Houghton), 1929 June 18; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, #137
      Reverse: "Not Built" stamped 1929
    - Note for map #130 (map is not attached), (Quantity 0) (Drawer F 5, Folder 3)
      Homes, Map #130.
    - hundreds of blueprints and drawings from a number of different Rockefeller family properties, including Forest Hill in Cleveland., BLUEPRINT (Drawer R 1)
    - hundreds of blueprints and drawings from a number of different Rockefeller family properties, including Forest Hill in Cleveland., BLUEPRINT (Drawer R 2)
    - hundreds of blueprints and drawings from a number of different Rockefeller family properties, including Forest Hill in Cleveland., BLUEPRINT (Drawer R 3)
    - GENERAL PLAN OF THE EYRIE GARDEN FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HARBOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1933; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 6)
      "THIS PLAN SUPERCEDES ONE OF SEPT 1928; CORRECTED FOR 1930"; LABELED ON REVERSE "FROM MRS. PANARD", LABELED "3.18 (a)"
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR THE ANNUAL GARDEN FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HARBOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 8)
      "CORRECTED FOR 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935"; LABELED "4.02"
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR EAST BORDER, GARDEN FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HARBOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1931-1935 February 25; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 8)
      "CORRECTED FOR 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935"
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR EAST BORDER OF LAWN, FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HABOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1931-1935 February 19; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 8)
      "CORRECTED FOR 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935"; LABELED 4.07
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR WEST BORDER OUTSIDE GARDEN, FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HARBOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1931-1935 February 18; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 8)
      "NO CHANGES FOR 1931, CORRECTED FOR 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935", LABELED 4.06
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR WEST BORDER OF LAWN, FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HARBOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1931-1935 February 18; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 8)
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR NORTH BORDER OUTSIDE GARDEN, FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HABOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1930-1934 February 6; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 7)
      "CORRECTED FOR 1930, 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934"
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR EAST BORDER OUTSIDE GARDEN, FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HARBOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1930-1931; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 3)
      "SEPT 1930, CORRECTED FOR 1931"; LABELED 4.03
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR SOUTHWEST CORNER OF THE EYRIE GARDEN - PART II, FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HARBOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1929 Spring; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 3)
      LABELED 4.07 (b)
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR SOUTHWEST CORNER OF THE EYRIE GARDEN,FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HARBOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1928 October 5; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 2)
      LABELED 4.07
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR WEST BORDER OUTSIDE GARDEN, FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HARBOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1931-1933 March 2; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 6)
      LABELED 4.06; "NO CHANGES FOR 1931, CORRECTED FOR 1932, 1933"
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR EAST BORDER OUTSIDE GARDEN, FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HARBOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1931-1932 April 6; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 5)
      LABELED 4.03; "CORRECTED FOR 1931, 1932"
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR EAST BORDER OUTSIDE GARDEN, FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HARBOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1931-1932 March 10; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 5)
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR NORTH BORDER OUTSIDE GARDEN, FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HABOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1930-1932 March 26; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 5)
      LABELED 4.05, "CORRECTED FOR 1930, 1932"
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR EAST BORDER OF LAWN, FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HABOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1930-1932 March 11; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 5)
      LABELED 4.07; "CORRECTED FOR 1931, 1932"
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR EAST BORDER OF LAWN, FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HABOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1931-1933 March 1; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 6)
      LABELED 4.07; "CORRECTED FOR 1931, 1932, 1933"
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR WEST BORDER OF LAWN, FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HARBOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1931-1933 April 26; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 6)
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR THE ANNUAL GARDEN FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HARBOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1932 April 27, 1933 February 28; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 6)
      LABELED 4.02; "CORRECTED FOR 1932, 1933"
    - NORTH BORDER OUTSIDE GARDEN, EYRIE GARDEN AT SEAL HARBOR (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1928 March; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 2)
      LABELED 4.05
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR SOUTH BORDER, EYRIE GARDEN AT SEAL HARBOR (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1928 March; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 2)
      LABELED 4.04
    - EAST BORDER OUTSIDE GARDEN, EYRIE GARDEN AT SEAL HARBOR (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1928 March; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 2)
      LABELED 4.03
    - WEST BORDER OUTSIDE OF GARDEN, EYRIE GARDEN AT SEAL HARBOR (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1928 March; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 2)
      LABELED 4.06
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR GARDEN, EYRIE GARDEN AT SEAL HARBOR (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1928 Spring; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 2)
      LABELED 4.03 (a)
    - EAST BORDER OUTSIDE GARDEN, EYRIE GARDEN AT SEAL HARBOR (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1929 March; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 3)
    - NORTH BORDER OUTSIDE GARDEN, EYRIE GARDEN AT SEAL HARBOR (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1928 Spring-1929 March; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 3)
    - WEST BORDER OUTSIDE OF GARDEN, EYRIE GARDEN AT SEAL HARBOR (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1929 March; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 3)
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR SOUTHWEST CORNER OF THE EYRIE GARDEN - PART I, FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HARBOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1928 Spring-1929 March; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 3)
      LABELED 4.07 (a)
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR SOUTHWEST CORNER OF THE EYRIE GARDEN - PART II, FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HARBOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1929 Spring; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 3)
    - THE EYRIE GARDEN (SEAL HARBOR, MAINE) ((ASSUMED TO BE BEATRIX FARRAND)), 1928 September 23; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 2)
      LABELED 3.18
    - PRELIMINARY PLANTING PLAN, EYRIE GARDEN AT SEAL HARBOR (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1927 October; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 1)
      LABELED 4.01
    - WEST BORDER OUTSIDE OF GARDEN, EYRIE GARDEN AT SEAL HARBOR (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1928-1930; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 4)
    - GARDEN PLAN FOR THE EYRIE ESTATE OF MRS. JDR, SEAL HARBOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), undated; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 2)
    - PLANTING PLAN FOR THE ANNUAL GARDEN FOR JDR JR ESQ AT SEAL HARBOR, MAINE (BEATRIX FARRAND, LANDSCAPE GARDENER), 1932 April 27; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 6, Folder 5)
      "CORRECTED FOR 1932"
    - PLANTING PLANS FOR ANNUAL AND PERENNIAL GARDENS, THE EYRIE, SEAL HARBOR, MAINE, 1983; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 7) (Drawer F 6, Folder 8)
  - Real Estate, 2.L
    - miscellaneous maps from Upper West Side of New York City, near Fort Tryon (George C. Wheeler), 1915-1935; MAP (Quantity 7) (Drawer B 1, Folder 10)
  - Religious Interests, 2.N
    - Additions to Parish Hall
      - 3 Surveys of Old and New Property Lines of Union Church- Pocantico Hills., 1929 July, December; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 3) (Drawer B 1, Folder 90)
      - Union of P.H Comm. Center; addition to parish hall. Wyeth & King Architects (see correspondence 1954, April 27), 1955 January 17; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 6) (Drawer B 1, Folder 90)
      - Topographical Survey prepared for Union Church of Pocantico Hills, 1954 April 6; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 1, Folder 90)
      - Survey of property prepared for Union Church of Pocantico Hills (4 copies) Note attached to first page from J.Farrell to Mr. Gumbel, 1954 September 20. (Chas H. Sells), 1954 July; MAP (Quantity 4) (Drawer B 1, Folder 90)
      - Sketch plan showing proposed children's building as an addition to the parish hall and suggested road layout. (see correspondences of 1954 November 22-23), RENDERING (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 1, Folder 90)
      - photocopies of "Addition to parish hall," Union Church. (Wyeth & King Architects), 1954 November 23; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 3) (Drawer B 1, Folder 90)
      - Site plan showing proposed children's building as an addition to the parish hall and suggested road layout. Union Church-Pocantico Hills (Wyeth & King Architects), 1955 January 17; MAP (Quantity 4) (Drawer B 1, Folder 90)
      - "Alteration and additions to parish hall," Union Church-Pocantico Hills-Final report to advisory board from the Building committee, 1955 May 31; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 5) (Drawer B 1, Folder 90)
      - Survey of parsonage lot belonging to JDR Jr. (scale 1" = 50') (Walter Kidde Constructors Inc.), 1938 June; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 1, Folder 90)
      - Survey of portion of Magee lot prepared for JDR Jr. (scale 1" = 2') (Walter Kidde Constructors Inc.), 1938 October; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 1, Folder 90)